nick-asia.com 2014-06-26

# Nick Asia | Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS

Welcome! This Privacy Policy governs this website and online services owned and operated by Nickelodeon Asia (the “Nickelodeon Asia Site” or "Site", as the case may be). By accessing the Nickelodeon Asia Site, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes what information the Nickelodeon Asia Site collects from users, including children, when they visit the Nickelodeon Asia Site; how such information is used and stored; when such information may be disclosed to third parties; how users, parents, and guardians can control the use and disclosure of collected information; and how information is protected. 

Our visitors’ privacy is important to us, and we recognize the need to provide additional privacy protection for children on the Nickelodeon Asia Site permitting such visitors. Our privacy practices are guided by the Personal Data Protection Act 2012, as well as other Singapore data privacy directives and regulations. Younger visitors should always check with their parents or guardians before entering information on any website and we encourage families to discuss their household guidelines regarding the online sharing of personal information. 

SUMMARY

For your convenience, the following is a quick summary of our Privacy Policy. Please read the entire Privacy Policy for more detailed information. 

I. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE.

We may request or collect certain information when you visit the Nickelodeon Asia Site. However, visitors are required to share only the information that is reasonably necessary to participate in the particular activity. 

A. Registration Information:  The information required to register varies by Site, but may include: (a) birth date; (b) gender; (c) country; (d) city/ province; (e) zip code; (f) user name and password; (g) wireless telephone number; (h) email address; and (i) other profile information such as avatar preferences, communications preferences, and interests. If you are under the legal age of consent for your country, we strongly recommend that you seek your parents’ permission before registering. For certain countries, visitors or their parents will receive an activation email and must follow the procedures or otherwise agree to the terms within the activation email within a certain time period to activate the account; accounts not activated within that time period will be deleted. 

Registration information is used to enable visitors to take advantage of site offerings; respond to visitor’s requests for products, services, and information; serve appropriate material; customize the content you see when you visit the Nickelodeon Asia Site; and offer visitors special offers and promotions from the Nickelodeon Asia Site and the “Viacom family of companies” (which comprises Viacom International Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates), as well as on behalf of selected third parties offering products, programs or services, that we believe may be of interest to you. 

B. Social Platform Registrations and Social Media Plugins:  The Nickelodeon Asia Site permits or requires you to register or log into your account via a social networking platform such as Facebook Connect, or permits you to use social media plugins such as the Facebook “Like” or Google “+1” buttons. When you use these social networking platforms and plugins, your username and password for the services and other information available about you or collected from you on these services may be shared with us. 

When you use social networking platforms and plugins, you share your information with them and their privacy policy applies to their collection, use, and disclosure of such information. In addition, they may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on the Nickelodeon Asia Site, and they may notify your connections on the social networking platform about your use of the Nickelodeon Asia Site. Such services may also employ unique identifiers which allow your activity to be monitored across multiple websites for purposes of delivering more targeted advertising to you. For more information about Facebook Connect, please go [here](http://www.facebook.com/help/). Please note that their privacy policies may be different from our own and we encourage you to read them. 

C. Computer Information Collected by Us:  When visitors come to a Site, we automatically collect certain information from their computers or mobile devices, such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the visitor's IP address, the web browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome and Firefox), UDID (for mobile devices), information about the websites visited before and after visiting the Site, the web pages and advertisements viewed and links clicked on within the Nickelodeon Asia Site, interactions with e-mail messages sent by the Site or the Viacom family of companies (e.g., links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded), information collected through the use of unique identifiers such as cookies (see below), information regarding the Internet service provider, and other standard server log information ("Computer Information"). 

We may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies (on the Nickelodeon Asia Site. "Cookies" (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are text files that help store user preferences and activity. “Web beacons” (also known as image tags, gif or web bugs) are small pieces of code used to collect advertising data, such as counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses. The Site and/or third parties may use “cookies”, “web beacons” and other similar tracking technologies (collectively, “Tracking Technologies”) to collect Computer Information automatically as you browse the Site and the web. 

By visiting the Site, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, understand and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of the Site through these Tracking Technologies and Identifiers and that we may use Tracking Technologies in the emails we send to you. 

Our Third Party Advertising Service Providers (as defined in Section D) do not have access to Tracking Technologies set by the Nickelodeon Asia Site except to the extent necessary to provide services to the Site. The Third Party Advertising Service Providers, as well as advertisers, may themselves set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your Device if you choose to have Tracking Technologies enabled in your browser (or, for Flash cookies, if you have not removed them) and/or they may otherwise have access to other information about you. 

You have a number of options with respect to the Tracking Technologies set by the Nickelodeon Asia Site: 

  * You can prevent the use of certain Tracking Technologies (other than Flash cookies) by using the controls in your Web browser. To do so, you must complete both of the following steps: 

  * Delete existing Tracking Technologies through the “Internet Options” sub-option of the “Tools” menu option of your browser or otherwise as directed by your browser’s support feature; and 
  * Disable future Tracking Technologies by using the same browser controls. Additional information on disabling most Tracking Technologies may be available through your browser’s support feature. (See the “help” section of your browser for more information.) 

  * You may be able to have the device you use to access the Nickelodeon Asia Site warn you each time a cookie or most other Tracking Technologies is being set (other than Flash cookies), or you can choose to turn off such warnings. This is done through your browser on the device you use to access the Nickelodeon Asia Site. Additional information on warnings and removal of warnings may be available through your browser’s support feature. 

Please note that deleting, rejecting, disabling or turning off Tracking Technologies through the above options will not remove Flash cookies. For more information about Flash cookies and how to remove them from your computer, please visit [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 

Please be aware that certain areas and features of Nickelodeon Asia Site can only be accessed in conjunction with Tracking Technologies, and that disabling Tracking Technologies might prevent you from accessing such content. 

D. Computer Information Collected By Others:  Nickelodeon Asia Site uses a variety of third-party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers, and other third-party service providers (collectively, “Third Party Advertising Service Providers”) to, for example, serve advertisements on the Nickelodeon Asia Site, facilitate targeting of advertisements, and measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on the Nickelodeon Asia Site (“Targeting Services”). These Targeting Services enable us to display advertisements based on your visits to the Nickelodeon Asia Site and other websites you have visited and may include delivering advertisements or other content for products and services that may interest you. Targeting Services also help prevent you from seeing repeated advertisements and enable us to research the usefulness of certain advertisements. 

These Third Party Advertising Service Providers do not have access to Tracking Technologies set by the Nickelodeon Sites except to the extent necessary to provide services to the Nickelodeon Sites. The Third Party Advertising Service Providers, as well as advertisers, may themselves set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your device if you choose to have Tracking Technologies enabled in your browser (or, for Flash cookies, if you have not removed them) and/or they may otherwise have access to Other Information about you. In addition, Third Party Advertising Service Providers may collect aggregate log data separately and independently from what the Nickelodeon Sites collect. 

You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other websites you encounter on the Internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not the Nickelodeon Sites. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your information and this Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that they may collect from you. We encourage you to research and direct any of your questions in this regard to these third parties. Use of a third party’s Tracking Technology is subject to their own privacy policies. 

With respect to the Tracking Technologies set by Third Party Advertising Service Providers and advertisers (and outside the control of the Nickelodeon Sites), you have a number of options: 

  * You can opt-out of the use of information for these advertising purposes by the Third Party Advertising Service Provider DoubleClick by using those Providers’ opt-out tools. You can access DoubleClick’s tool at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/>. We also may from time to time permit other Third Party Advertising Service Providers and Advertisers to collect Information on the Nickelodeon Sites. Some of these Providers and Advertisers may participate in the Network [Advertising Initiative’s Opt-Out Tool](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and/or the [Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Please click on the links to these tools to learn more about your choices. 
  * Please note the following with respect to opting out of Tracking Technologies set by Third Party Advertising Service Providers and advertisers: 
  * The opt-out tools discussed above are “cookie based.” This means that the tools rely on cookies to remember your choices with respect to the use of your information by the parties that offer you those choices. If you opt-out but then use the controls in your browser to delete all Tracking Technologies, you may have to opt-out again, a second time, in order to re-establish your opt-out preferences. 
  * Opt-outs are browser-specific. This means, for example, that if you opt out while using Internet Explorer 9, this choice will not affect the collection of information collected by Tracking Technologies when you use Mozilla Firefox on the same device. It also means that opting out on one device will not affect the collection of information by Tracking Technologies on other devices you may use to access the Nickelodeon Sites. 
  * You also can prevent the use of certain Tracking Technologies (other than Flash cookies) on a particular device by using the controls in your Web browser. To do so, you must complete both of the following steps: 

  * Delete existing Tracking Technologies through the “Internet Options” sub-option of the “Tools” menu option of your browser or otherwise as directed by your browser’s support feature; and 
  * Disable future Tracking Technologies by using the same browser controls. Additional information on disabling most Tracking Technologies may be available through your browser’s support feature. (See the “help” section of your browser for more information.) 

  * You may be able to set the device you use to access the Nickelodeon Asia Site warn you each time a cookie or most other Tracking Technologies is being set (other than Flash cookies), or you can choose to turn off such warnings. This is done through your browser on the device you use to access the Site. Additional information on warnings and removal of warnings may be available through your browser’s support feature. 
  * Opting-out of, deleting, rejecting, disabling or turning off Third Party Advertising Service Providers’ Tracking Technologies does not mean that you will no longer receive online ads. Opting-out of, deleting, rejecting, disabling or turning off Third Party Advertising Service Providers’ Tracking Technologies only means that such ads will no longer be tailored to your specific viewing habits or interests, but you will continue to see ads on the Nickelodeon Sites. 
  * PLEASE NOTE THAT THE USE AND STORAGE OF FLASH COOKIES TYPICALLY CANNOT BE CONTROLLED THROUGH YOUR BROWSER. For more information about Flash cookies and how to remove them from your computer, please visit [here](http://kb2.adobe.com/cps/526/52697ee8.html)

E. Contests and Sweepstakes:  The Nickelodeon Asia Site may offer online contests and sweepstakes. To enter these contests and sweepstakes, you may be required to provide your first name and email address and/or additional information required for the management of the contest or sweepstakes. We may collect e-mail address in the contest or sweepstakes, store email address for the duration of the sweepstakes, and use it for notification if the winner. 

F. Electronic Postcards and Messages:  Some Nickelodeon Sites provide visitors the opportunity to send electronic postcards and “wish lists” of items they want to family or friends, which means we will send, on the visitor’s behalf, email messages to family and/or friends. To do so, visitors must provide the email address of the recipient of such electronic postcards or email messages. Email addresses provided to us for this purpose are used solely to send the requested postcard or email message and are deleted from our system once the postcard or message is sent. In some cases, we may offer visitors an incentive (e.g., points to be used in an online game) for referring information about products to the visitor's family or friends. In such cases, we will comply with all applicable legal requirements. Please note that this feature may not be available to visitors in certain regions. 

G. Electronic Newsletters:  Visitors can provide their email addresses to receive email newsletters and promotions from Nickelodeon Asia, the Viacom family of companies, and our business partners. Visitors may change their preferences regarding emails at any time through the unsubscribe link in the newsletters or by logging into and changing the preferences for their account on the Site. If you are under the legal age of consent for your country, we strongly recommend that you seek your parents’ permission before signing up to receive newsletters from us. 

H. Geolocation Information:  We may collect and store information about your precise geographic location if you enable your computer or mobile device to send us location information. You may be able to change the settings on your computer or mobile device to prevent it from providing us with such information. We use this information, for example, to enable visitors to take advantage of Site offerings; respond to visitor’s requests for products, services, and information; manage games; customize the content visitors see when visiting the Nickelodeon Sites; and to offer visitors special offers and promotions from Nickelodeon Sites and the Viacom family of companies, as well as on behalf of selected third parties offering products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to our visitors. 

I. Other Data Collection and Use:  We collect search query information when visitors search for information on the Nickelodeon Asia Site. We also collect information from visitors when they contact us with questions and comments. 

We may use this information, along with any of the other information described above, to (i) analyze use of the Nickelodeon Asia Site and understand and improve our service offerings; (ii) prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; and (iii) for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent. 

We may use this information, along with any of the other information described above, to (i) analyze use of the Nickelodeon Asia Site and understand and improve our service offerings; (ii) prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; and (iii) for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent. 

We may combine information collected through the Nickelodeon Asia Site with information we collect from other sources (e.g., social media integration services), other Viacom family of company’s sites, offline records or publicly available information). It is your responsibility to provide complete and accurate information and to keep such information up to date. We are not responsible for any problem or liability arising from your failure to do so. 

II. DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES.

We may share your information with third parties for the limited purposes described below. In Singapore, parents of children under the age of consent have the option of consenting to the collection and use of their child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to certain third parties. 

A. Law Enforcement and Safety.

You acknowledge, consent, and agree to the extent legally permissible in this jurisdiction to allow us to access, preserve, and/or disclose the information we collect and/or content you provide to us to a law enforcement agency or other third parties if required to do so by law or with a good faith belief that such access, preservation, or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce the Terms of Use of the Nickelodeon Asia Site; (c) respond to claims that the content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the owners of the Nickelodeon Asia Site, any user of the Nickelodeon Asia Site, a third party or the general public. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of others. 

B. Agents.

Information collected through the Nickelodeon Sites may be transferred, disclosed or shared with third parties engaged by us to handle and deliver certain activities, such as sweepstakes and contests, e-cards and newsletters, and to perform other technical and processing functions, such as sending postal mail and email, maintaining data integrity, programming operations, user services or technology services. We may provide these third parties information collected as needed to perform their functions, but they are prohibited from using it for other purposes and specifically agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information. Some of these agents may request additional information during the course of offering their services. Before you provide additional information to third party agents, we encourage visitors to review their privacy policies and information collection practices. 

C. Third Parties/Advertisers.

Some Nickelodeon Sites partner with outside third parties to provide you with additional content, products, or services that we believe may be of interest. For example, we may partner with a greeting card company, software manufacturer, or social media plugin provider to offer you electronic cards, or social networking, functionalities. These partners operate websites and services that are separate and independent from the Nickelodeon Sites and, accordingly, may have their own privacy policies. If you consent or register with one of our partners, that means you grant the Nickelodeon Sites permission to give your registration and other information, including e-mail address, to that third party. 

In addition, Third Party Advertising Service Providers may use their own Tracking Technologies to gather information about you. Please see Section I(D) above for more detailed information regarding such use of Tracking Technologies. 

For more information on our use of third party advertisers and the self-regulatory principles, please click [here](http://srp.mtvn.com/sitefaq.html)

D. Co-Branded Sites and Features.

The Nickelodeon Asia Site may from time to time offer co-branded services and features, such as events and promotions that we put together with another company ("Co-Branded Partner"). Such services may be hosted on the Site and/or our Co-Branded Partner's website. We may share your information with our Co-Branded Partner and your voluntary use of or participation in a co-branded service or feature means that you opt-in and affirmatively consent to both the Nickelodeon Asia Site and our Co-Branded Partner collecting and using the information you provided during registration and/or in connection with the specific co-branded feature for fulfillment, marketing or administrative purposes. If you wish to opt-out of a Co-Branded Partner's future use of your information for marketing purposes, you will need to contact the Co-Branded Partner directly. The Co-Branded Partner will be identified on the co-branded feature or service. 

E. Viacom and Other Affiliated Businesses.

The Nickelodeon Asia Site is part of the Viacom family of companies. Where permitted by law, we may share information we collect about you within the family of Viacom family of companies’ websites and other affiliated businesses so that we can, for example, provide you with information about products and services that might interest you. 

F. With Your Consent.

We may otherwise disclose your information pursuant to your consent. 

III. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER.

The Nickelodeon Asia Site is designed for and targeted to Singapore and South East Asian audiences and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of Singapore. We make no representation that the Nickelodeon Asia Site is operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of, or governed by, other countries. By participating in activities on the Nickelodeon Asia Site, you certify that you meet the age and other eligibility requirements for the Nickelodeon Asia Site as set forth in the Terms of Use Agreement. If you do not meet the age and other eligibility requirements please discontinue using the Site immediately as your continued use of the Site indicates that you are agreeing to the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Please be aware that by providing us with personal information, you understand and agree that: (1) due to our international operations, your personal information may be transferred to and stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction; (2) to the extent you are a resident of a country other than Singapore, you consent to the transfer of such data to Singapore for processing by our affiliates in accordance with this Privacy Policy and (3) the Privacy Policy and the collection of information pursuant to the Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore (including but not limited to the Personal Data Protection Act 2012), without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. 

If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Nickelodeon Asia Site because your use of the Site represents your consent. If you have already provided personal information, please contact us about how you would like us to handle such information. 

IV. SECURITY, STORAGE AND RETENTION OF INFORMATION.

The Nickelodeon Asia Site maintains reasonable technical and organizational steps to help ensure that information collected is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers and use of electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access. We limit access to visitor’s information to employees and contractors who are authorized for the proper handling of such information, and any employee found violating our standards of security and confidentiality will be subject to our disciplinary processes. We also take reasonable steps to help make sure our third-party agents protect the security of your personal information. However, as with most Internet sites or services, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully access such personal information through a number of means despite our efforts. 

Information collected at the Nickelodeon Asia Site will not be stored for longer than is necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, or to otherwise meet legal requirements. 

V. ACCESSING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION; TERMINATION OF WIRELESS SERVICES.

A. Reviewing Your Information

You have the right to access, update and correct factual inaccuracies in personally identifiable information that we collect online at the Nickelodeon Sites, subject to certain exceptions. To do so, you should log into your account. To help protect your privacy and the security of your personally identifiable information, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access. 

B. Parental Access

Parents/guardians of children under the age of 13 can print out and mail or fax us a signed form that allows them to review any personally identifiable information collected about their child, have this information deleted, and/or request that there be no further collection or use of their child's personally identifiable information. 

Anyone requesting personally identifiable information about a child and to ensure that the person is in fact the child's parent or legal guardian. 

VI. ONLINE SAFETY.

Some of our affiliates’ websites offer you and your child an online safety guide which we encourage you to use as starting point for discussing safety and privacy concerns with your child. Of course, involvement in your family’s online lives is the most important safety tool available. 

VII. LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES.

The Nickelodeon Asia Site may contain links to other sites, including those of sponsors, advertisers, social networking platforms, and survey companies. These other websites are governed by their own privacy policies or information collection practices, which may be substantially different from ours. We encourage visitors to other websites to review the privacy policies and information collection practices of those websites. 

VIII. YOUR RIGHT TO REQUEST PERSONAL DATA.

The Singapore Personal Data Protection Act 2012 and Malaysia Personal Data Protection Act 2010 permit our visitors who are domiciled in Singapore and/or Malaysia to request certain information regarding our retention and disclosure of their personal data. To make such a request, please send an email to the following respective country’s email addresses, or you may contact us via regular mail at the following respective country’s offices: 

**Singapore:**  
Email: [Sg.DPO@vimn.com](mailto:Sg.DPO@vimn.com)  
Address: Nickelodeon Southeast Asia Data Protection Officer  
c/o Nickelodeon Asia Holdings Pte Ltd  
151 Lorong Chuan  
#03-08 New Tech Park (Lobby H)  
Singapore 556741 

**Malaysia:**  
Email: [My.DPO@vimn.com](mailto:My.DPO@vimn.com)  
Address: Nickelodeon Southeast Asia Protection Officer  
c/o Viacom International Media Networks (M) Sdn Bhd  
L2.08, Level 2, Wisma BU8  
11, Lebuh Bandar Utama  
47800 Petaling Jaya, Selangor Darul Ehsan 

This document is the sole statement of the Nickelodeon Asia Site's Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid. In interpreting this Agreement, the English version governs the interpretation and meaning of the obligation set forth herein. To the extent there is an ambiguity or conflict with the Privacy Policy in other languages, the Privacy Policy in English governs. 

Top
